Teanna Tang

UX/UI Designer

Contact



Baltimore, MD 410-530-1312



in linkedin.com/in/ttang20/

Skills

User Research and User Testing Creating User Personas **User Flows** Wireframing and Prototyping User Interface Design Information Architecture Style Guides

Tools

Sketch Figma Adobe XD Balsamiq Marvel HTML CSS

Education

Feb 2022 - May 2022 Frontend Development Certificate CareerFoundry UX Design Program

Aug 2021 - Feb 2022 **UX Design Certificate** CareerFoundry UX Design Program

Aug 2016 - May 2020 **BS** Degree in Animal Sciences University of Maryland, College Park

Profile

Passionate UX Designer with experience in research and user-centered design. Skilled in creating wireframes and prototypes with tools such as Sketch, Figma, and Adobe XD. Comfortable working collaboratively or crossfunctionally to identify problems and design creative solutions.

Projects

Sept 2021 - Present

PlutoPay, Virtual Wallet App / CareerFoundry Case Study

- Applied a user-centered design process to design a responsive web app for online shopping and making online transactions
- Created interactive prototype with Adobe XD
 - https://xd.adobe.com/view/bbdacf12-1b64-4f05-94e8d2ebfee1c4d8-ee89/
- Case Study:
 - https://www.behance.net/gallery/135860833/PlutoPay

Aug 2021 - Sept 2021

Study Buddies, Flashcard App/CareerFoundry Case Study

- Conducted user interviews and surveys to gather research data to develop user personas, sitemaps, and user flows
- Created mid-fidelity wireframes with Figma:
 - https://www.figma.com/community/file/1091926616991 630583/Study-Buddies

Experience

2021 - Present

Dance Instructor/JAMZ Dance Studio

- Worked with many students with a variety of ages and skill levels
- Communicated with parents and staff to ensure all expectations and goals were met

2018 - 2020

Lab Researcher/Matrix Laboratories

- Conducted various research projects with laboratory team
- Collected project data
- Investigated problematic cases using effective communication with administration team